okay number eight asks which is the
lowest energy confirmation for
cyclohexene so this one's pretty
straightforward option A is chair let's
just draw the chair really quick and so
what we need to understand about the
chair is it does a couple of things
first it allows for all of the carbons
to obey the perfect tetrahedral geometry
that they enjoy for example we've got
two hydrogens right here we can
essentially imagine this as being a
wedge Bond and this as being a dash Bond
down to those other carbons but however
you want to visualize it it has that
perfect tetrahedral geometry with 109.5
degree Bond angles and then the other
thing it does is that all of the Newman
projections for all of these bonds would
put the different alkal groups as anti
to one another so for example this
carbon carbon bond is anti to this
carbon carbon Bond and you can do that
for all the carboncarbon bonds so number
one there are no eclipsing interactions
the alal are not eclipsing